Martin Mondaca

8419 W Hubbell St, Phoenix, AZ 85037 | (602) 573-1484 | martin7mondaca@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Most recently, employed as a Specimen Accessioner with LabCorp. Previously worked in customer service for State Farm Bank, Freshly, and most recently Macy's among others. Experience managing groups of up to 15 employees in retail with Forever 21; includes assisting in the interview process, hiring process, and training.

Skills and Abilities

Able to read and speak Spanish fluently. Able to type 65 words per minute. Excellent computer skills. Great communication skills with customers. Very fast learner and willing to grow.

Employment History

<u>LabCorp</u> Phoenix, AZ 07/2020 – 12/2020

Specimen Accessioner

- Process incoming specimen
- Image incoming paperwork onto digital database

<u>Amazon</u> Phoenix, AZ

Warehouse Associate 03/2020 - 07/2020

03/2015 - 02/2016

• Ensured merchandise was properly sorted for shipment.

<u>Macy's</u> Tempe, AZ 09/2019 - 02/2020

Platinum Customer Service Specialist

• Assist customers with placing orders, deliveries, and other inquiries.

<u>Freshly</u> Phoenix, AZ

CX Senior Chat Associate 02/2019 - 08/2019

- Assist customers with incoming inquires.
- Take on additional tasks as directed by upper management.
- Assist teammates with inquiries.

CX Chat Associate 06/2018 - 02/2019

• Assist customers with incoming inquires.

State Farm Bank Tempe, AZ

Customer Service Representative (Bilingual-Spanish) 03/2017 - 03/2018

- Take incoming calls from bank customers and assist with their accounts.
- Assist Agent members with customer bank products.

Forever 21 Peoria, AZ

Lead of Service 07/2016 - 03/2017

- Manage large groups of associates on sales floor.
- Track email and credit card sign up.
- Assist with store opening and closing tasks.

Sales Associate/Cashier 09/2015 - 07/2016

- Assist customers on sales floor, fitting room, and cash register.
- Helped in the training of new sales associates.

Grand Canyon University Phoenix, AZ

Jesus Carranza

IT Desktop Technician 04/2014 - 08/2015

- Assist university staff with IT issues both in person and over the phone.
- Ensure that IT issues were resolved in a timely and efficient manner.

Education

Grand Canyon University Phoenix, AZ 08/2012 – 08/2015

Maryvale High School Phoenix, AZ 08/2008 – 05/2012

References

Open Force (Team Lead)

623-293-6975